export const quizData = [
    {
        question:"What command is used to start the React local development server?",
        options:["npm serve","npm start","npm run dev","npm build"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question:"A copy of the 'real' DOM that is kept in memory is called what?",
        options:["Real DOM","DOM ","Virtual DOM","Shadow DOM"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question:"What tool does React use to compile JSX?",
        options:["JSX Compiler","React router ","Babel","ReactDOM"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question:"What is the default port number in which the application run?",
        options:["3000","3001","4000","8000"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is a way to handle data in React.js ?",
        options:["State & Props","Serbvices & Components","State & services","State & Components"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following is true regarding Babel ?",
        options:["Compiler","Transpiler","Both od the above","None of the above"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question:"In React.js, how we can pass the data from one component to another in React.js ?",
        options:["setState","Render with arguments","Props","PropTypes"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following method is true about referring parent class in React.js ?",
        options:["self()","inherits()","this()","super()"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question:"In React.js which one of the following is used to create a class for Inheritance ?",
        options:["Create","Extends","Inherits","Delete"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question:"Which keyword creates a constant in JavaScript?",
        options:["const","let","constant","var"],
        answer: 1
    }
]